(404) 751-6891 • brad@huchteman.com • hirebrad.com

Profile

Developer with 18 years of experience building websites and web applications including front-end development, back-end development, database design, social media integration, and HTML email.

Technical Knowledge

HTML, CSS, jQuery, PHP, Classic ASP, MySQL, MS SQL Server, Photoshop, Lightroom, responsive web design, Drupal, Wordpress, web accessibility

Work Experience

2013-2017

Rezora

Senior Software Developer

- Responsible for systems' email deliverability
- · Account setup for new clients
- · Development of new features and system enhancements
- Coding HTML email templates
- System Tech Support in Zendesk and LiveChat

2005-2007

Kellen Interactive

Web Developer

- Lead developer for Georgia Natural Gas and Ohio Natural Gas websites
- Drupal and Wordpress theming and customizations
- Developed social media strategies for clients
- Photographer for company events.

2005-2007

Web Hugh Inc.

Web Developer, Graphic Designer

- Developed all projects with focus on advanced CSS and standard compliant XHTML.
- Responsible for implementing design concepts to graphic designer's specifications.
- · Performed basic graphic design as needed.

2003-2005

G-A Communications

Web Developer

- Project lead and primary contact for the largest account, Safeway.com and all related Safeway branded sites (Vons.com, Carrsqc.com, Genuardis.com, and Everyseasonmag.com).
- Oversaw maintenance, redesigns, new development, and integration of third party systems for numerous Safeway sites and applications.
- Planned and performed weekly HTML and SQL updates to web and database content for all Safeway sites.

1999-2003

Distance & Distributed Learning, GSU

Technical Supervisor / Lead Web Designer

- Supervised the development, and maintenance of 30 websites and web projects.
- Worked closely with award winning faculty to create course content and interactive learning tools using Flash.
- Supervised a staff of 3 web designers, 1 graphic designer and 6 student employees.
- Provided faculty support to faculty web users at University.
- Worked with managers to produce all departmental reports and policies

Education

1998–2003 Georgia State University

Worked towards a BBA in Computer Information Systems

1997–1998 Georgia Perimeter College

Completed undergraduate core curriculum with a concentration in Spanish and Art.